{
    "id": "a781096502e649b0ae61c568ee9a6954",
    "title": "General Grammar Quiz (Gap Filling)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8361cbfdd03f4747a737e2324aee27c3",
            "title": "General Grammar Quiz (Gap Filling)",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I often ……………………….. horror movies.",
                    "description": "Use the simple present to talk about habits, routines etc. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "am watching",
                        "watch",
                        "watches"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………… tomorrow.",
                    "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about pre-planned future events. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "leave",
                        "am leaving",
                        "will leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ……………………………. in May.",
                    "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about pre-planned future events. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "marry",
                        "will marry",
                        "will get married",
                        "are getting married"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………………. care of stray dogs and cats.",
                    "description": "Use the simple present if this is a habit. The present continuous is used to talk about something that we are doing at the moment. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "takes",
                        "take",
                        "is taking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………….. run when I was just one year old.",
                    "description": "Use could to talk about past ability. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "could able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ………………………….. me you weren’t coming.",
                    "description": "Both expressions can be used to criticize people for not doing things. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "could tell",
                        "could have told",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There ……………………….. be a bakery in that corner.",
                    "description": "Use used to to talk about past habits and states.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was used to",
                        "would",
                        "used to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………………… talk about her illnesses for hours.",
                    "description": "Either would or used to can be used to talk about past habits. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "would",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………….. working so hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "am not used to",
                        "am not using to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Where is Samuel?’ ‘He ……………………… to Russia.’",
                    "description": "Has been is used to talk about finished visits. We use the present perfect to express ideas like these because he is still in Russia. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "has been",
                        "has gone",
                        "went"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We saw children ……………………….. in the park.",
                    "description": "After see, we can use an ing form or an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "play",
                        "to play",
                        "playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You never let me ………………………… a sentence.",
                    "description": "Finish is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "to finish",
                        "finish",
                        "finishing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}